

### **Gustavo Jaques**

## Career Summary

Addicted, dedicated and resilient bilingual frontend and backend professional (english, spanish and portuguese). Focused on newest stacks on the market and over than 16 years of experience.

Solid and concrete skills in C#, Typescript, Javascript & Java. Nonetheless, real knowledge on its frameworks and libraries .Net, Angular, React and Spring.

# Summary of Qualifications

Experienced In:

.Net, Angular, Spring, React, C#, Java, Typescript, Javascript, Html, Css, Photoshop.

### Languages

- Spanish (intermediate)
- English (advanced)

# Career History

### PRIVACY, São Paulo, Brazil

Mar 2021 – Mar 2022

• Portuguese (fluent)

Software Architect & Developer

- Software Architect (API)
- User Information & Experience (Atomic Design)
- Cloud Architect
- Angular 11 Developer
- Asp.Net Core Mvc Developer
- Database Administrator

### THE SKYLINE AGENCY, Dallas, USA

Jan 2014 – Dec 2018

Full Stack Developer (Remote)

- Development (ASP.NET, PHP, MVC, MVVM)
- Chop (convert) Photoshop to HTML / JS / CSS
- Database (MS Sql Server & MySql)
- Open Source CMS (SparkPay, Wordpress, Drupal & Magento)
- Team Leader (Brazil / Canada / India & Eua)
- Motion effects for websites (After Effects & Javascript)
- SEO Optimization & Performance

## **WORLDCELLOS, São Paulo, Brazil**

Jan 2014 - Dec 2018

Chief Executive Officer

- Development (C, C++, C#, Objective-C, ASP.NET, AS, CSS, HTML)
- Projects Web, Software, App & Embedded Systems
- Integration & Rest API (fluorineFX,amfPhp,Wsdl...)
- Motion design & Rich media (After Effects, Flash and Javascript)
- Database (NoSql, MS Sql Server & MySql)
- Outsourcing: NaturezzaHumana, Oxxy e Crane.is

#### Education

Universidade Nove de Julho, São Paulo, Brazil

BS in Computer Science

Jan 2018 – Jan 2022